(Penny:)Okay, listen to me.
(Penny:)Playing games is not gonna help
get Amy back.
(Sheldon:)I am not trying to get her back.
(Sheldon:)But out of curiosity, what is a way?
(Penny:)All right, honey,
Iet me tell you a story.
There was a guy I Iiked,
and I never told him how I feIt.
(Penny:)Eventually, he started going out with
someone else and I always regretted it.
(Penny:)Do you see where I'm going with this?
- I believe I do.
- Hmm.
(Sheldon:)I'm the guy.
(Penny:)You're not the guy.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
That would explain so much.
(Sheldon:)Your constant presence
in my apartment...
(Sheldon:)...that baffling dalliance with Leonard
just to be near me...
(Sheldon:)...the way you call me sweetie
all the time.
- I call everyone sweetie.
- You tramp.
(Sheldon:)Ugh.
(Penny:)Look, Sheldon, all I'm saying
is strap on a pair and go talk to Amy.
Strap on a pair? Wait. Of what, skates?
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, you are so not the guy.